Seeno, gulp channel, go-go!
Today we are going to do a frame dance.
This is the first time for me to do a frame dance, and you can see a black frame here,
This is a challenge video to see if you can dance within the frame.
I see. This is the first time for you to do a frame dance, isn't it?
I've done a lot of dance projects.
We've never done a "coverer" type of dance either.
Isn't it interesting? Eight dancers in this room.
Usually it's about 1 3 minutes.
Really.
Family date, about 2 minutes.
About 2 minutes.
About 1.5 minutes.
By the way, the music is Quick.
There's a floor dance, but that looks hard.
Well, let's stand up.
Standing.
Because of the costumes.
Sorry, it's a costume thing.
This time we'll stand.
And this one?
That, too.
Better than here.
Certainly.
But this is still a swing.
Yes, that's what I'd like to do.
Start the video!
This time, I am wearing Teeholic's costume.
Let's start the frame dance!
You didn't do anything today, right?
Oh, that's right.
We'll go in one swathe at a time.
Cool.
From here.
That's enough?
That's enough, right?
Not yet?
Not yet.
Oh, no.
My foot's coming back.
It might be too narrow.
It's too narrow.
It's really in there.
Do you want to go in between?
I made a mistake.
Oh, here it comes.
But I gave the wrong signal.
What's this?
Oh, here it comes!
Everyone, this way, please.
I can't do it!
It's so tiny!
To the left.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, come on.
Oh, here it comes.
Oh, here it comes!
It's funny that Masao hid the dance by themselves.
Shall we play at least one more song?
We'll do one more song, for now.
We already did it earlier.
You did?
What do we do now?
This is about right.
Can you get the taste?
Does it come across on the screen?
I can't really say.
But, you know, make it one, two, three, four boards smaller.
About the size of a bathtub.
Isn't it big enough?
That's a big bath.
It's impossible. It can only hold one person.
Three can fit.
I don't think I can do this. It's too tight.
I'm putting in three people vertically just now.
Let's go to the countdown for the second song.
Let's start the music!
I made it tiny.
Vertical.
Tekebanban tekebanban tekebanban, can you hear me?
Three, two, one, teke-ban-ban, teke-ban-ban, teke-ban-ban.
This countdown is starting to bother me more and more.
I'm getting more and more curious about it.
I asked my friends about it, and they told me.
I'd rather have a camomile than a yes.
I got a nice experience
I got a nice experience.
It's a matter of time
Oh, I found my mind
I'm your girl
Plenty of impressions, your mind, me, mine
My first event.
Tik Tok, TikTok, I think I hear you.
I can hear the aura in your chest.
Oh, why don't you go right ahead?
Oh, everyone's coming in.
I'm feeling good.It looks good.
Can we go?
Yeah, it's quick.
I'm ready.
Okay, just stop.
Stop. Stop. Stop.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Sorrow.
blowspremium
Oh, no...
I was wrong.
But I don't want to regret it.
Feel not at all
Trouble
Everything will be alright
Tick-tock tick-tock
I can hear you
Alarm in my chest
No more jokes
Oh my
Thinking bomb heartbeat
They're gonna hear it
Heart
Countdown in my heart
Chitty-bang-bang, chitty-bang-bang, chitty-bang-bang, they'll hear it
321 Chitty bang bang, chitty bang, chitty bang, chitty bang, chitty bang
Heart countdown. Yay. Upload.
Tickety-tick, tickety-tick, tickety-tick. Maybe he's feeling it, too.
Countdown in my heart.
The Ação Cassinça, I can't do it.
That means it's too small.
Challenger.
But then which is it? Width? Height or width?
Vertical?
I want to do it again.
I'm talking about the number of songs, not the width.
You know, the ones we used to sing.
Monster Gal.
Love Jenny.
It's true, it means a lot to move around.
Yes, it does.
Is it this wide?
Right here, right here.
Okay, so like a series of dots.
He's pissed.
I've never been mad at you.
Let me try.
Please let me try.
Too tiny.
Please, please, please, please.
What do I look like?
On the side.
Make it a foot taller.
Let's do it, let's do it, let's do it.
Can you see it?
Oh, my God.
Same stage.
Vertical.
It's exactly 100 centimeters tall.
Look, it's sticking out.
About 150 centimeters.
150 centimeters.
That's Kira and Yoh.
That's right.
Kira and Yoh?
Kira and Yoh.
Good luck!
Next, in order of age.
Let's start.
♪
One, two, three, four.
♪♪
Oh, no.
You're more beautiful than I thought.
♪♪
You live for me
If you want me to laugh
If you wish to laugh at me
This is so awesome!
Super cute
Hey, me too, Harikid
Let's party again
yeah
me
It's warm.
What's the theme?
Tough.
Yes, it is.
What?
How?
Come on!
Open up!
WINTER VELYever
Cool!
Combine!Let's do it!
Let's see!
It's fine.
Please call me on any stage.
Even if it's this small, we'll do it.
I'll do it anywhere.
We can do it on an elevator.
Bigger.
As long as Yohka and Kira are in there.
I can do it.
That's what this video is about.
I'll deliver it anywhere for now.
Snow.
Snow, Tatechou.
Thank you for watching to the end.
If you like this video, please leave a high rating, comment, or subscribe to our channel.
Bye bye.